{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Stone Siding Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40142/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40142,"taskName":"Brick or Stone Siding: Install or Completely Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Completely Replace Brick or Stone Siding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Stone Siding Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":219,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Brick wall walkway walk steps","textMessagingName":"Inst Mason Siding","rolloverLongDesc":"Increasingly popular in recent years, stone or brick siding can provide a traditional look for any home.","rolloverShortDesc":"Veneers often used as realistic alternatives to natural stone or brick.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Completely Replace Brick or Stone Siding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Stone \u0026 Brick Siding Installation \u0026 Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick or Stone Siding Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick or Stone Siding: Install or Completely Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Siding Project","urlName":"Brick-or-Stone-Siding-Install-or-Completely-Replace","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Stone \u0026 Brick Siding Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Brick,wall,walkway,walk,steps,sidewalks,patio,masonry,flooring,floor,bricks,paver,mason,Siding,Stone","emcCategoryOid":-12008,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":453,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40142/":{"taskOID":40142,"originalTaskOID":40142,"setID":453,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1056,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5686,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Siding for a new home","answerDisplayText":"Siding for a new home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5685,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding for a new addition","answerDisplayText":"Siding for a new addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5261,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing siding","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5312,"questionDisplayText":"Masonry Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of masonry do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6108,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1114,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17314,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Real Stone","answerDisplayText":"Real Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17315,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Real Brick","answerDisplayText":"Real Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200160,"questionDisplayText":"Home's current siding","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of siding is currently on the home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1059,"questionDisplayText":"Stories of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1056,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5686,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Siding for a new home","answerDisplayText":"Siding for a new home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5685,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding for a new addition","answerDisplayText":"Siding for a new addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5261,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing siding","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5686,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Siding for a new home","answerDisplayText":"Siding for a new home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5685,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding for a new addition","answerDisplayText":"Siding for a new addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5261,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing siding","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5312,"questionDisplayText":"Masonry Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of masonry do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6108,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1114,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17314,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Real Stone","answerDisplayText":"Real Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17315,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Real Brick","answerDisplayText":"Real Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6108,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1114,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17314,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Real Stone","answerDisplayText":"Real Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17315,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Real Brick","answerDisplayText":"Real Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200160,"questionDisplayText":"Home's current siding","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of siding is currently on the home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1059,"questionDisplayText":"Stories of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}